Finding Aid for the Sterling Silliphant Papers, 1957-1985
UCLA Library, Department of Special Collections
Sterling Silliphant Papers
1957-1985
1079
Silliphant, Stirling, 1918-
120 boxes (61 linear ft.) 1 oversize box.
Collection consists of film and television scripts by Silliphant. Also includes correspondence, clippings, and production notes.
University of California, Los Angeles. Library. Department of Special Collections. Los Angeles, California 90095-1575
Administrative Information
Restrictions on Access
COLLECTION STORED OFF-SITE AT SRLF: Advance notice required for access.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of Stirling Silliphant, 1969-85.
Biography
Silliphant was born on Jan. 16, 1918 in Detroit, MI; graduated magna cum laude from Univ. of So. Calif., 1938; worked in advertising and promotion for Walt Disney and 20th Century Fox until 1952; produced a few films in the 1950s before becoming a screenwriter for both feature films and television; his successful television series include Naked city and Route 66; films include The Joe Louis story (1953), In the heat of the night (1967), Charly (1968), Marlowe (1969), The Poseidon adventure (1972), The towering inferno (1974); won an Academy Award for In the heat of the night in 1967; was a prolific novelist who published more than 50 books; moved to Thailand in late 1980s, where he was active in developing the region's film industry; died in Bangkok on Apr. 26, 1996.
Scope and Content
Collection consists of film and television scripts by Silliphant. Also includes correspondence, clippings, and production notes.
Organization and Arrangement
Collection arranged by title.
Indexing Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
Subjects
Silliphant, Stirling, 1918---Archives.; Screenwriters---California---Los Angeles---Archival resources.
Genres and Forms of Material
Film scripts.; Television plays.
Related Material
Stirling Silliphant Collection. Available at Arts Library Special Collections, UCLA.
Container List
- Personal material
  - Specifications design no. P-1112, 1975 November (Box 104, Folder 19)
    Auxiliary steel ketch designed for Mr. Stirling Silliphant, John C. Alden, Inc., Boston
  - [Indian rights - South Dakota], 1981 (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Specifications for construction of Silliphant Residence, Incline Village, Nevada, 1972 August; David Jay Flood, AIA Associates.; [2 copies] (Box 105, Folder 3-4)
  - General correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - General correspondence, 1978 (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - General correspondence, 1977 (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - General correspondence, 1976; [2 folders] (Box 108, Folder 4-5)
  - General correspondence, 1975; [2 folders] (Box 108, Folder 6-7)
  - General correspondence, 1974; [2 folders] (Box 108, Folder 8-9)
  - General correspondence, 1973; [3 folders] (Box 109, Folder 1-3)
  - General correspondence, 1974 (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - General correspondence, 1972; [2 folders] (Box 109, Folder 5-6)
  - Speeches, ca. 1972-1975 (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - Biography and photographs, 1975 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Round the world trip, 1975 (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - The Caucus [correspondence], 1976-1979 (Box 110, Folder 10)
  - Karate, 1964-1972 (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - General correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - General correspondence, 1968 (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - General correspondence, 1969; [2 folders.] (Box 114, Folder 3-4)
  - General correspondence, 1970 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - General correspondence, 1971; [2 folders.] (Box 115, Folder 1-2)
  - Miscellaneous corrrespondence, 1977-1983 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook, 1956 (Box 121, Folder 1)
    [clippings re Stirling Silliphant]
    Box 121 is an oversize flat box, 15-1/2" x 18-1/2".
  - Scrapbook, 1952-1953; Produced by Stirling Silliphant. (Box 121, Folder 2)
    [primarily re film "The Joe Louis Story"]
  - Income from writing., 1957.; 1 folder. (Box 33)
  - Miscellaneous business correspondence., 1955-1962.; 1 folder. (Box 33)
  - Income from writing., 1958.; 1 folder. (Box 33)
  - Personal correspondence., 1959.; 1 folder. (Box 33)
  - Record of earnings., 1960.; 1 folder. (Box 33)
  - Correspondence., 1960-1961.; 1 folder. (Box 33)
  - Correspondence., 1961.; 1 folder. (Box 33)
  - Miscellaneous., undated.; 1 folder. (Box 33)
  - Writing log., Blank forms. (Box 34)
- Production material
  - Gold project, undated (Box 104, Folder 18)
- Professional material
  - Air dates., 1959. (Box 34)
  - TV writing credits, 1977 (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - Daily schedules, undated (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - Daily schedules, 1974 (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - Daily schedules, 1973; [2 folders] (Box 110, Folder 6-7)
  - Writing schedule, 1968, 1972 (Box 110, Folder 8)
  - Writing class (accepted), 1962 (Box 110, Folder 9)
  - TV market list (story editors), 1966 (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - Writers, 1968 (Box 110, Folder 12)
  - Academy writers branch members list, 1970 (Box 110, Folder 13)
  - National Academy of TV Arts Sciences I, 1966-1968 (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - National Academy of TV Arts Sciences II, 1968-1973 (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - National Academy of TV Arts Sciences, ca. 1965-1973; Books. (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - Speaking engagements, 1966-1971 (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Chrysler Theatre royalty plan, 1972 (Box 113, Folder 5)
- Research material
  - Research on sexuality, 1975 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    Re "Surrogate".
  - China, no dates (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - "Attitudes Toward Premarital, Extra-marital and Homosexual Relations in the U.S. in the 1970s", 1979 May; Glenn, Noral D. Weaver, Charles N. (Box 104, Folder 3)
    Journal of Sex Research.
  - "Recreational Sexuality Preferences Among Middle-Class Husbands and Wives", 1978 May; Mancini, Jay A. Orthner, Dennis K. (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - "Sexual History and Present Sexual Behavior of Cohabiting and Married Couples", 1978 February; Markowshi, E.M., Croake, J.W. Keller, J.F. (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - "Swinging in Retrospect", 1976 August; Fang, Betty. (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - "Permissive Attitudes Toward Sexual Behaviors: A Clarification of Theoretical Explanations", 1978 August; Laner, Mary Riege, Laner, Roy H. Palmer, C. Eddie. (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Sexual Law Reporter, 1977, 1978 (Box 104, Folder 8)
    Excerpts.
  - Sexual Law Reporter, 1975-1976, 1979 (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - Emory Law Journal. "Constitutional Law -- Right of Privacy ... ", 1979 (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - West's Missouri Digest., 1979 December (Box 104, Folder 11)
    Sections on sodomy, rape from UCLA Law Library
  - Annotated Missouri statues, 1978, 1979 (Box 104, Folder 12)
  - Missouri Criminal Code, 1979 (Box 104, Folder 13)
  - "Morality for the 70's" and "The Decline and Fall of Sex", 1976 February (Box 104, Folder 14)
  - [Clippings and articles], ca. 1981-1983, undated (Box 104, Folder 15)
  - [Memos re sexual offenses and the criminal law], 1981 (Box 104, Folder 16)
  - Time cover story. "The Convening of America", 1978 December 18 (Box 104, Folder 17)
  - Gold, ca. 1950 - (Box 105, Folder 1)
    Re: gold coins.
  - Novel (Gold Hustlers), 1972-1973 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - [Clippings and magazines - various topics], 1978 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Holding file, ca. 1970-1979 (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - The next 25 years of our lives, 1973 (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - Research for police shows, 1963-1976 (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - Porn novel, 1976-1977 (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - [Civil strife], 1968 (Box 114, Folder 5)
- Writings by others
  - [Vietnam Sunset] by James Brachman, 1975 (Box 115, Folder 6)
    With letter of transmittal, 17 April 1975.
  - Mercury Jones, 1977; by Edwin H. Blum; outline (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - [Indianapolis story], 1976 (Box 117, Folder 2)
    With letter from Franklin Konigsberg and outlines.
  - [Proposed motion picture story by Doug Laurence?], undated (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Chalk, 1972; by Mark Weingart (Box 117, Folder 4)
    With letter of transmittal from Joel Rogosin, 5 July 1972.
  - "Chip's Harvest", undated; by Peggy Phillips (Box 117, Folder 5)
    [episode of TV series, My Three Sons]
  - Havoc, undated; by Michael Brodie, Nicholas de Grunwald, Gordon Flemying; screenplay (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - The Fountains of Paradise, 1977 April; by Arthur C. Clarke; movie outline (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - The Seventh Power, 1976; by James Mills (Box 117, Folder 8)
    With letter of transmittal from Robert Bookman, 13 May 1976.
  - Swap, undated; by Walter Wager; second draft revised screenplay (Box 117, Folder 9)
    Production # 00211.
  - The Letter, undated; by Jim Stinkley James Wainwright; an original story for the screen (Box 117, Folder 10)
  - Break of day ..., undated; by Robert L. Dellinger; first draft original screenplay (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Nine, undated; by James Tugend; screenplay (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - The Guards, undated; by Tak Kubota Robert Payne; original synopsis and series format (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Meteor !!!, 1976 November 22; by Steven Bach; screenplay (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Rx Nightingale One, undated; by Milo (?) O. Frank (Box 118, Folder 5)
    Blake Edwards Entertainment.
  - Centerfold, undated; by Alexander Singer Judith Singer; original screenplay (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - A Touch of Murder, 1972 November; by Derek Marlowe; screenplay (Box 118, Folder 7)
    Based on the novel "A Touch of Death" by Charles Williams.
  - The Amazing Nelly Bly, 1975 November; by Susan Bernard; treatment (Box 118, Folder 8)
    With letter of transmittal from Susan Bernard, 17 March 1976.
  - Prize of Peril, 1974; by Robert Sheckley (Box 118, Folder 9)
    With letter of transmittal from Walter M. Mirisch, 19 August 1974.
  - The Lost City, 1969; by Erwin Hillier (Box 118, Folder 10)
    Original story outline and script suggestions.
  - The Tokyo Hostages, 1975; by Grard de Villiers (Box 118, Folder 11)
    Translated by Lowell Bair.
  - Ocean Realm, undated; introduction by Sylvia A. Earle (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - [Re books by others], 1973, undated (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Submissions, 1971 (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - Submissions, 1970 (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - Submissions - I, 1969 (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - Sumissions - II, 1969 (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - All My Children ..., undated; created and written by Agnes Nixon [Bible] (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - Ryan's Hope [Bible], undated; [Index to characters] (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - Frank - Jill - Seneca, 1977 (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Nona, undated; by Stephen King; [2 folders] (Box 119, Folder 10-11)
  - Gordon Entertaining Nightly, undated; by Paul Hampton Richard Pryor, original story by Paul Hampton; screenplay (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Hell's Kitchen, 1975; by Sylvester Stallone; original screenplay (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Jerusalem's Lot, 1975 December 12; by Stephen King; [title page - p. 150] (folder 1 of 3) (Box 120, Folder 3)
    North Windham, Maine.
  - Jerusalem's Lot, 1975 December 12; by Stephen King; [p. 151-326A) (folder 2 of 3) (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Jerusalem's Lot, 1975 December 12; by Stephen King; [p. 327-550] (folder 3 of 3) (Box 120, Folder 5)
- Writings by Stirling Silliphant
  - Articles, Addition, 11/82.
    - Te Deum. n.p., 1979 March 22; by Stirling Silliphant.; 16 pages. Typescript with holograph corrections. (Box 103, Folder 8)
      An article written for the Writers' Guild of America Magazine.
      - With this. Another copy. n.p., 1979 March 22; 13 pages. Typescript (carbon), incorporating changes made in the typescript copy. (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - Novels
    - Pearl. n.p., undated.; Written by Stirling Silliphant.; 87 pages. Typescript (carbon). (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Pearl. n.p., undated.; Written by Stirling Silliphant.; 87 pages. Typescript (carbon). (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Pearl. n.p., undated.; Written by Stirling Silliphant.; 83 pages. Typescript, typescript (photocopy) with holograph corrections. (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - Pearl. n.p., undated.; Written by Stirling Silliphant.; 83 pages. Typescript (photocopy). (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - [Pearl] n.p., ca. 1978; ca. 150 pages. Typescript (photocopy). Many duplicate pages. (Box 102, Folder 10)
      Miscellaneous pages of novel.
    - [Pearl] n.p., ca. 1978; ca. 150 pages. Typescript (photocopy), typescript. (Box 102, Folder 11)
      Portion of the novel.
    - Steel Tiger. v.p., various dates; by Stirling Silliphant.; 5 items. (Box 103, Folder 12)
      Ephemera regarding publication of Steel Tiger.
    - Steel Tiger. v.p., 1983; by Stirling Silliphant.; ca. 15 items. (Box 103, Folder 13)
      Publicity regarding Steel Tiger. Bay Area publicity.
    - Bronze Bell, undated; novel, typescript with corrections (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - John Solo, 1981 May; 2 copies. (Box 105, Folder 6)
      New series of paperback novels to be written by SS.
    - Steel Tiger, 1982 August (Box 105, Folder 7)
      A John Locken adventure.
    - Steel Tiger, 1983 January 28; author's galleys (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - John Solo novels, 1981 (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Short Story
    - Under Saturn., Typescript. 36 pages. (Box 27)
- Teleplays.
  - A New Kind of Love
    - 1971 December 21., Ten copies of revised section, typescript. (Box 53)
    - 1971 December 7., Five copies of second draft of typescript pilot script. (Box 53)
    - 1971 December 13., Five copies of revised section, typescript. (Box 53)
    - 1971 December 22., Ten copies of revised section, typescript. (Box 53)
    - 1971 December 28., Six copies of revised section, typescript. (Box 53)
  - A Repertoire of Sly Devices. n.p.
    - 1962 October 6, 1 final draft teleplay. (Box 18)
    - 1962 November 12, 1 revised teleplay. (Box 18)
    - 1962 November 5., 1 first draft teleplay. (Box 18)
  - A World of Love, [formerly "A New Kind of Love"]
    - Correspondence. (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Newsclippings and promotional releases. (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Production schedules. (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Meeting and concept notes. (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Story outlines., undated.; Typescript multilith. Two copies. (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - [Script], 1971 November 1; Typescript. (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - [Script], 1971 November 1; Typescript carbon with holograph corrections. (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Pilot script [screenplay]., 1971 November 3; First draft. Typescript multilith. Two copies. (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Pilot script [screenplay]., 1971 December 6; Revised draft with holograph corrections. (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Pilot script [screenplay]., 1971 December 6; Revised draft. Typescript carbon. (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Pilot script [screenplay]., 1971 December 6; Revised draft. Typescript photocopy. Two copies. (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Pilot script [screenplay]., 1971 December 7; Second draft, part one. Typescript multilith. (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Pilot script [screenplay]., 1971 December 7; Second draft, part one. Typescript multilith. Three copies. (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - [12-13-71], 1971 December 13 (Box 62, Folder 4)
      - Pages from pilot scriopt to be revised., Typescript multilith. No revisions. (Box 62, Folder 4)
      - Revised pages for pilot script., Typescript multilith with holograph corrections. (Box 62, Folder 4)
      - Revised pages for pilot script., Typescript. (Box 62, Folder 4)
      - Revised pages for pilot script., Typescript photocopy. (Box 62, Folder 4)
      - Revised pages for pilot script., Typescript multilith. Three copies. (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Revised pages for pilot script., 1971 December 18; Typescript multilith and typescript with holograph corrections. (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Revised pages for pilot script., 1971 December 21; Typescript multilith. Two copies. (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Revised pages for pilot script., 1971 December 22; Typescript multilith. Two copies. (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - [12-28-71], 1971 December 28 (Box 62, Folder 8)
      - Pages from pilot script to be revised., Typescript multilith. No revisions. (Box 62, Folder 8)
      - Revised pages for pilot script., Typescript multilith with holograph corrections. (Box 62, Folder 8)
      - Revised pages for pilot script., Typescript carbon. (Box 62, Folder 8)
      - Revised pages for pilot script., Typescript multilith. (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Captain Sinbad, King Brothers Productions, Inc.
    - Various pages of teleplay with numerous holograph corrections. (Box 1)
    - 1964 July 23, 1 teleplay (carbon). (Box 1)
    - 1964 July 23, 1 teleplay. (Box 1)
    - 1964 July 8, 1 teleplay (2nd copy) with holograph corrections. (Box 1)
    - 1964 July 8, 1 teleplay with holograph corrections. (Box 1)
    - 1964 July 1, 1 first draft teleplay. (Box 1)
    - 1964 June 1, 1 story outline (carbon). (Box 1)
    - 1964 June 1, 1 story outline with holograph corrections. (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, etc, relating to teleplays
    - Route 66., undated; Lancer Productions, Inc.; 1 folder. (Box 25)
      Correspondence.
    - Naked City., undated; Shelle Productions, Inc.; 1 folder. (Box 25)
  - Death of Princes
    - 1959 November 28, Typescript [teleplay] (Box 41)
  - Gold Coast, n.p.
    - 1960 April 4, 1 story outline. (Box 1)
    - 1960 March 10, 1 prospectus. (Box 1)
    - 1960 April 14, 1 first-draft teleplay. (Box 1)
  - Golden Gate, Lin Bolen Productions, Inc.; Addition, 11/82.
    - Golden Gate. n.p., 1979 December; Written by Stirling Silliphant.; 137 pages. Typescript (carbon) with holograph corrections. (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Golden Gate. n.p., 1979 December; Written by Stirling Silliphant.; 137 pages. Typescript (carbon). (Box 94, Folder 7)
      - Another copy., Typescript (photocopy). (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Golden Gate. n.p., Cover date is 1979 December 17; Written by Stirling Silliphant.; 126 pages. Typescript (multilith). First draft. (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Golden Gate. n.p., 1980 March; Written by Stirling Silliphant.; 126 pages. Typescript (multilith) with holograph corrections. First revised first draft. (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Golden Gate. n.p., 1980 March; Written by Stirling Silliphant.; 128 pages. Typescript (carbon). (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Golden Gate. Beverly Hills., 1980 May 7; by Stirling Silliphant.; 127 pages. Typescript (multilith). Revised second draft. (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Golden Gate. Beverly Hills., 1980 May; by Stirling Silliphant.; 127 pages. Typescript (multilith), typescript with holograph corrections. Third draft. (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Golden Gate. Beverly Hills., 1980 May; by Stirling Silliphant.; 127 pages. Typescript (carbon). Third draft. Some pages are stained. (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Teleplay. Beverly Hills., 1980 June 6; by Stirling Silliphant.; 96 pages. Typescript (multilith), typescript with holograph corrections. Final shooting script. (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Teleplay. Burbank., 1980 July 2; by Stirling Silliphant.; 111 pages. Typescript (photocopy). Revised final shooting script. (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Teleplay. Burbank., 1980 July 2; by Stirling Silliphant.; 111 pages. Typescript (photocopy). Revised final shooting script. (Box 96, Folder 1)
      Another copy.
    - Revised pages. n.p., ca. 1979-1980; by Stirling Silliphant.; ca. 125 pages. Typescript, typescript (carbon), typescript (photocopy), typescript (multilith) with holograph corrections. (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - It Takes a Thief. n.p.
    - 1965 November 22, 1 pilot teleplay with holograph corrections. (Box 17)
  - Longstreet
    - (Box 38)
      Writers - correspondence, stories and meeting notes.
    - (Box 38)
      Casting; Credits; Fanmail; General correspondence and story outlines; Insurance Information Institute correspondence; Meeting notes; Music; Correspondence with Oliver Nelson, composer; Pilot - correspondence; Sponsors; Stories.
    - Correspondence I and II., 1971-1972 (Box 39)
    - Music. (Box 39)
    - Contract corresondence with writers and directors. (Box 40)
    - Story outlines by various writers. (Box 40)
    - Longstreet introduction, character backgrounds and brief descriptions., (photocopy) (Box 40)
    - 1970 October 12., 2 copies of revised first draft, typescript teleplay. (Box 44)
    - 1970 August 18., Storyline, typescript. (Box 44)
    - undated., Carbon. (Box 44)
    - 1970 August 14., Typescript, conception. (Box 44)
    - 1970 August 28., 3 copies of typescript teleplay. (Box 44)
    - 1970 August 29., Typescript section with holograph corrections, teleplay. (Box 44)
    - 1970 October 15., Second draft teleplay, typescript with holograph corrections. (Box 44)
  - Maya, Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer, Inc.
    - 1966 November 15, 2 copies of pilot teleplay. (Box 1722)
    - 1966 May 15 - 1967 June 29, 10 teleplays and revisions. (Box 1722)
    - 1967 January 18, 2 copies of teleplay (for the second show of the series). (Box 1722)
    - 1966 September 16, 6 copies of presentation and pilot teleplay. (Box 1722)
    - Correspondence, etc relating to teleplays, 2 folders. (Box 25)
    - Correspondence, etc relating to teleplays, undated; 1 folder. (Box 25)
      Work orders.
    - Correspondence, etc relating to teleplays, undated; 1 folder. (Box 25)
      "Interoffice Communications."
    - (Box 32)
      Premise and format.
    - 1967., Scripts. (Box 32)
    - Maya, Caper of the Golden Roe, 1967 March 28 (Box 107, Folder 1)
      With revised pages, 3/29/67.
    - Maya, Deadly Passage, 1967 June 29; changes 6/29/67 (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - Maya, Caper of the Golden Roe, 1967 March 28; [with holograph corrections] (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Maya, Caper of the Golden Roe, 1967 March 28; [carbon copy with holograph corrections] (Box 107, Folder 4)
      With revised pages, 3/29/67, with holograph corrections.
    - Maya, Blood of the Tiger, 1966 November 15; final. [2 copies] (Box 107, Folder 5-6)
    - Maya, Blood of the Tiger, 1967 January 8; final shooting scrip (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - Maya, Blood of the Tiger, 1966 May 16; With extensive holograph corrections. (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - Maya, Blood of the Tiger, 1966 May 23; With holograph corrections. (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - Maya, Blood of the Tiger, 1966 May 16; [carbon copy] (Box 107, Folder 10)
    - Maya, Blood of the Tiger, 1966 May 23; [carbon copy] (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - Movin' On
    - Correspondence (Box 39)
    - Pilot (Box 39)
    - Publicity (Box 39)
    - Newsclippings (Box 39)
    - 1971 October 22., Three copies of final revised shooting script, typescript. (Box 48)
    - 1971 October 5., Typescript of pilot script. (Box 48)
    - 1971 September 29., Carbon of pilot script. (Box 48)
    - 1971 September 24., Typescript of pilot episode. (Box 48)
    - 1971 September 22., Typescript with holograph corrections of pilot script. (Box 48)
    - 1971 October 5., Typescript with holograph corrections of pilot script. (Box 48)
    - 1971 September 29., Typescript with holograph corrections of pilot script. (Box 48)
    - 1971 October 16., Final revision of typescript pilot script (carbon). (Box 48)
    - 1971 October 18., Final revised shooting script, typescript. (Box 48)
    - 1971 October 16., Final revision of typescript with holograph corrections of pilot script. (Box 48)
  - Mr. Novak, Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer, Inc.
    - 1964 May 6, 1 teleplay (carbon). (Box 1)
    - Correspondence and agreement between the author and the producer (Box 1)
      Folder.
    - 1964 April 14, 1 story outline (carbon). (Box 1)
    - 1964 April 14, 1 story outline with holograph corrections. (Box 1)
    - 1964 May 6, 1 teleplay with holograph corrections. (Box 1)
    - 1964 April 14, 2 copies of story outline (carbon). (Box 1)
  - Naked City, Shelle Productions, Inc.
    - 1958 July 31 - 1963 May 3, 45 teleplays. (Box 2-5)
    - 1959 May 7 (Box 34)
      Re-run schedule.
  - New Centurions
    - New Centurions - television., 1973 March 2.; Typescript and typescript carbon. (Box 39)
      Second draft presentation format for series.
    - New Centurions - television., Typescript with holograph corrections. (Box 39)
      First draft of presentation format for television series.